Is it okay to feel invited?
呼ばれだらしくいい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you being called?
呼ばれてる?
Yeah.
うん
Enough?
もういい?
Okay, should I go home?
よし、帰るかな?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going home?
帰る?
Okay, let's put it in.
よし、入れてみる
Take it first when cooking.
着料理で最初に取って
Whoa, someone stuck in the uniform.
おー、制服についちゃったよ、誰か
Hey.
ねー
Okay.
いい よ
Where where?
どこどこ?
Don't get bored, let me give you this.
退屈を得ないで、これあげてみよう
That's right, let's try that system made in the deep sea.
そうそう、深海製のその体制でやってみようぜ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
Look, this guy is with me.
ほら、こいつ一緒
To.
に
good?
いい?
I'll do it right away.
さ っさとやってあげる
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
strong.
強い
yes.
はい
OK, then.
OK、じゃあ
Let's rotate.
回転しようぜ
good.
うまい
I feel like it's going to be too soft.
柔らかくいっちゃいそうになるな
nice.
いいね
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
How about the back?
バックどう?
The back feels good.
バック気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I feel like it's going to be too soft.
柔らかくいっちゃいそうになるな
Shall we go first?
最初に行こうか
The back is amazing.
バックすごい
Does the back feel good?
バック気持ちいい?
good.
うまい
I feel like I'm going to go back.
バックいっちゃいそうになる
dangerous.
あぶない
It's moving.
動いてる
It moves naturally.
自然で動いてる
How about the back?
バックどう?
The back feels good.
バック気持ちいい
I feel like I'm going to go back.
バックいっちゃいそうになる
dangerous.
あぶない
fast air.
速い空気
Well, let's go first.
じゃあ、最初に行こうか
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
入れちゃうね
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
I entered.
入った
It's in.
入ってるよ
Chemp is better after all.
チェンプのほうがいいやっぱ
The real thing is better.
本物のほうがいい
Look here.
こっち見て
camera.
カメラ
Bangs are terrible.
前髪やばいね
Did you cut your bangs?
前髪切ったの?
Look again.
もう一回見て
One more time.
もう一回
Neck pink.
首 ピンク
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Che
チェ
I think it's better to use a pump.
ンプ のほうがいいやっぱ
The real thing is better.
本物のほうがいい
Did you cut your bangs?
前髪切ったの?
Yeah.
うん
bangs cut
前髪切
Did you?
った の?
Abu
あ ぶ
do not have.
ない
What happened?
どう なってた
Shall we go in soon?
そろそろ入っちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Can I give you a card?
カードしちゃっていい?
picture?
え?
Can I intervene?
口出していい?
Yeah.
うん
It's the mouth.
口だよ
mouth?
口?
Are you coming out?
出るの?
It's coming out.
出るのね
Yeah.
うん
I'm holding it so I can put it inside.
持つから中に入れちゃいそう
That's a lie.
嘘じゃん
It's dangerous, seriously.
あ ぶない、マジで
My bangs are really tight.
めっちゃ前髪締まりが
Because it's okay.
いい から
Well then, today too.
じゃ、 じゃあ今日も
Yeah.
うん
I'll be leaving soon.
そ ろそろ行っちゃうよ
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Can I show my face?
顔出しちゃっていい?
picture?
え?
Can I tell you?
お口出していい?
Yeah.
うん
It's your mouth.
お口だよ
Mouth?
お口?
Eh, Vero?
え、ベロ?
Above the tongue.
ベロの上
A dangerous feeling.
あ ぶ ない気持ち
It looks like it's going to come out because I'm holding it.
持つから中に出ちゃいそう
That's a lie.
嘘じゃん
It's dangerous, seriously.
あぶない、マジで
My bangs are really tight.
めっちゃ前髪締まりが
It's okay.
いいから
Okay, okay.
よし、オッケー
Well then, let's go.
じゃ、行っちゃうよもう
Okay, I can go.
よし、行けるよ
Will it come out?
出る?
Okay.
いいよ
Squat down more.
もっとしゃがんで
More, more, more.
もっと、もっと、もっと
Can you see further down, down, down?
もっと下、下、下、見える?
Yeah.
うん
Further down.
もっと下
picture?
え?
Oh yeah, there.
そうそう、そこ
Give me more.
もっと出して
I can give you more.
もっと出せるよ
I'll go.
行くよ
a,
あ、
Vero appeared.
ベ ロ出た
I got really excited.
めっちゃ精神出ちゃった
Nose, on the nose.
鼻、鼻に
Wait, Vero.
待って、ベロ
Okay, show me.
オッケー、見せて
Did it come out?
出た?
Take it out, take it out, use your hands.
出して、出して、手で
show me.
見せて
It sank too low.
下に垂れすぎたな
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出た
copper?
どう?
The smell of semen.
精子の匂い
Does it smell like fish?
魚の匂いする?
copper?
どう?
nose...
鼻...
It was a huge queen hit in my nose.
鼻の中めっちゃクイーンヒットした、
perhaps.
多分
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Okay, wait, let's just clean up a little and laugh at the end.
じゃ、待って、最後で、ちょっとだけ掃除して笑おう
Only the tip.
先っぽだけね
Yeah.
うん
Just the tip, look at it.
先っぽだけ、ほらさっきの
Damn it.
やべろ
A little bit of remaining sperm.
残りの精子ちょっと
It's all over.
パクって終わった
Okay.
オ ッケー
Well then, take it out and finish it.
じゃあ、出して、最後
Will it come out yet?
まだ出る?
It's still coming out.
まだ出る
Huh, is that sperm?
え、それ精子?
Eh, behind.
え、後ろの
Eh, sperm?
え、精子?
Eh, which one?
え、どっち?
I don't know.
わかんない
Okay.
オッケー
Well, how was it?
いやー、どうだった?
Lastly, let me know what you think.
最後、感想聞かせて
Finally, something.
最後、なんか
Finally, it's inside my nose.
最後、鼻の中入ってる
So, in the end, I wanted you to go even lower.
じゃあ、最後、もっと下に来てほしかった
But it was good.
でも、よかった
No, seriously, it was amazing, I was so patient when I went there.
いや、マジ、すごい、行くと超我慢してたんだよ、
最後
I was about to go for a while, but
もう、ちょっと行きそうだったけど、
It's a bit of an angle.
ちょっとアングルがね
Well, let's do it again.
じゃあ、またやろうよ
Yeah.
うん
Will we do it again?
またやる?
What will you do next?
次、何でやる?
Cosplay.
コスプレ
Next, uh, nurse.
次、えっとね、ナース
Oh, nice, nurse.
おー、いいね、ナース
Let's do it with a nurse.
ナースでやろうよ
Yeah.
うん
Nurse or Tsukuru Mizukine.
ナースもしくは、つくるみずきね
Tsukumizuki.
つくみずき
Yeah.
うん
Okay.
オッケー
Is it okay?
いいっすか?
Well, let's do it again.
じゃあ、またやりましょう
bye bye.
バイバイ
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ